http://www.saltlaketogo.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
The Salt Lake Convention and Visitors Bureau (SLCVB) is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. SLCVB collects information from site visitors at various locations on our Web site. Other than as disclosed in this statement or at the point of collection we will not sell, share, or rent this information to any third party unless required to do so by law. On this website we collect demographic data from Google's Interest-based advertising with Google Analytics. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network Ads using the Ads Settings
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie on our site is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information. If a site visitor rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to rejecting a cookie is that functionality may be limited in some areas of our site. Cookies enable us to track the interests of our site visitors to enhance our site. Some of our business partners also use cookies on our site (for example, the Trivia Game). We have no access to, or control over, these third-party cookies.
IP addresses
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track movement throughout the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual.
Links
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that SLCVB is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our site visitors to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by www.visitsaltlake.com.
Requests for Information, Newsletters, Surveys, Contests
If a site visitor requests information or wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information (such as name and e-mail address). From time to time, we request information via surveys and contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the site visitor therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose the requested information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address) and demographic information (such as age and zip code). Contact information collected for contests will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used to better understand our visitors and to improve this site.
Security
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our site visitors' information. Sensitive information submitted via the Web site is protected both online and offline. When a registration/order form asks for sensitive information (such as a credit card number), that information is protected with the best encryption software in the industry—SSL. We also take measures to protect information offline. Access to all collected information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific task are granted access to personally identifiable information.
Choice/Opt-out
Our site visitors are given the opportunity at the point where we ask for the information to decide if it may be used for purposes not directly related to our site. Site visitors who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out at any time by using the provided unsubscribe link.
Remarketing/Retargeting Policy
This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who have not completed a task on our site or visited key pages, for example requesting a visitors guide. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone's past visits to the [CLIENT NAME] website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google's privacy policy. You can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's Ads Settings. Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, this page will be updated to reflect the changes so our site visitors are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Get the latest articles, ski reports and Salt Lake deals by signing up for the Ski City newsletter.
Cookies are used for measurement, ads and optimization. By continuing to use our site you agree to our privacy policy.
